Anders G. Nordby





DESCRIPTION

Anders is a project manager, systems architect and senior developer with customer focus and many years of experience in the industry. He holds the **PRINCE2 Practitioner**, **PRINCE2 Foundation** and **Certified Scrum Master** certifications, and he has also had the role of *team leader* and *scrum master* in several projects.

WORK EXPERIENCE

05.2019 - PRESENT

Delichon AS

Daily Manager, Systems Architect & Senior Developer

Customer: Element Logic Duration: 3,5 years

Roles: Senior Systems Developer, Security Champion

Technologies: Akka.NET, Blazor, Vue.js, C#, Microsoft .NET Standard, ASP.NET, TeamCity, Octopus Deploy, Git, Powershell, Kiuwan. **Responsibility:** Senior developer on Element Logic's main product, eManager. Additionally, focuses on application security, and is the initiator and leader for Element Logic's Security Chapions Guild.

Customer: ABB

Role: Senior systemutvikler **Duration:** 6 months

Technologies: Azure DevOps, Azure DB, Azure WebServices, Akka.NET, TypeScript, React JS, C#, Microsoft .NET Core, TFS, Git, Powershell.

01.2018 - 04.2019

Sopra Steria

Lead Software Engineer

Roles: In-house architect responsible for planning and QA of offers to customers. Senior developer for some customers.

Customers: Skatteetaten, Helsedirektoratet.

Technologies: C#, .Net, Episerver CMS, ASP.NET MVC, Microsoft SQL Server, JavaScript, Jira, Confluence, TFS, Git.

03.2014 - 08.2017

CGI

Senior Web Developer

Roles: Team-leder, scrum master, hands-on architect.

Customers: ASKO, Fellesforbundet, Tekna, PIA, Miljødirektoratet. **Technologies:** C#, inRiver PIM, Apptus eSales, Episerver CMS, Episerver Commerce, IdentityServer, T-SQL, NServiceBus, Jira, Confluence, jMeter, BlazeMeter, Angular.js, Knockout.js.

o3.2010 – 01.2014 Making Waves, Senior Systems Consultant
o8.2008 – 12.2009 Creuna, Consultant / Systems Developer
o2.2006 – 07.2008 Ocelluz, Systems Developer & Project Manager
I0.2004 – 02.2008 Anders Nordby Konsulenttjenester
O5.1995 – 06.2002 Ajilon, Consultant

KEY COMPETENCIES

Processes

Systemarkitektur, Scrum, Kanban, prosjektledelse.

Development

C#, Akka.Net, Episerver CMS, Episerver Commerce, ASP.Net, Apptus eSales, inRiver PIM, IdentityServer, T-SQL, PL/SQL, JavaScript, JSON, NServiceBus, WebServices, REST, WebAPI, XML, HTML, CSS, jQuery, PowerShell, LATEX.

Tools

Jira, Confluence, Git, TFS, SubVersion, ReSharper, NewRelic, jMeter, BlazeMeter, NuGet.

CERTIFICATIONS

202I	Certified Optimizely Developer
2020	Microsoft Azure Fundamentals
2019	PRINCE2 Practitioner
2019	Certified Scrum Master
2018	PRINCE2 Foundation
2016	Certified inRiver Developer

COURSES

2019	Tom Gilb: Architecture Workshop
2018	Sopra Steria: Arkitekturskolen
2015	Microsoft: Lead Enterprise Architect Programmo

EDUCATION

2003 – 2004	University of Oslo, Teacher Training
1999 – 2000	Oslo Business Academy, IT Candidate
1987 – 1996	University of Oslo, Cand.Mag.
1984 – 1987	Eikeli High School, Natural Sciences

AWARDS

2013-2017 Episerver Most Valued Professional

LANGUAGES

EXCELLENT	Norwegian (native), English
NTERMEDIATE	Bulgarian
BEGINNER	Spanish, German, Japanese